I'm Nao Sakura, Dragon Blue from Team Statch.
I'm Yuka Yasumori of Iginari and Oyakusan!
Hey there!
This is our first time!
I don't know why they were chosen.
I'm so surprised!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
This time...
I think it's a post-production, but for me, it's a little bit of a localism, and there are other localisms in Tohoku and Nagoya, right?
So, I'd like to have a discussion among the members beyond the boundaries of the localism.
It's like Kai... Yes, yes.
Commonalities... No...
Yes, that's right.
But first of all, this outfit isn't in character, is it?
Waka-chan, first of all, you're not a character.
Which are you going to wear today?
Today, I'm going to wear what I have in mind, but not what I look like.
I see. Is that how you are usually seen? Usually, too.
What do people usually say about your first impressions?
But you look like an old man?
I thought you looked like an old man.
I agree with you.
I think I look like an old man, but when I talk, people say I look like a gal.
But your hair is a bit flashy.
I feel like a gyaru when I wear clothes like that.
But when I wear something like this, I look like a gal.
It suits me. It suits my face.
It just goes with you.
I think I would look good in Lolita style.
Today, I felt like I have potential.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Do you have any? I've had a talk with her before.
I was made to wear it once for a live photo shoot.
I didn't like it at the time, but everyone was forced to wear Lolita.
We all did it together.
But when I tried it on, I felt like I could totally pull it off.
You can wear it comfortably, can't you? The face definitely fits.
And I don't want to see them in a goth style, I want to see them in a sweeter style.
Oh no.
Everyone is saying "No, no, no.
I'm sure it'll look good on you.
But I really want to look this way.
I really want to be here.
That's right.
You're a gal, right?
We don't have any gals.
Do you have any gal friends? Someone who looks like a gal.
Yuzuki.
Yuzuki is not a gyaru, but rather a donkey.
I'm not a gal, I'm a donkey.
It's great.
Donpen-kun.
Dongpen-kun's character changes.
He was great on our team.
He went on line right away and said, "What are we going to do about this?
It's a big news.
But it's true that he might be more like a gal.
Inside, they wear jerseys and stuff.
I felt that Mizuki was amazing. Gal mindset.
Really? Do we smell the same?
We smell the same.
But, Waka, I thought you were a spring pusher.
I like everyone.
That's what's so great about them.
There's too much good in everyone.
Really?
I don't know what to do.
But my Yuna...
Nao, you're a big fan.
Thank you very much.
But it's fun to watch.
It's really fun to see that.
But I haven't been able to go out to eat with her once yet.
I'm surprised. I felt like I thought I was going.
I guess everyone around me thinks so, too.
But our schedules don't match at all.
It's too far away. It's a long distance.
Aichi and Sendai.
I think they would be happy to know that it's a long distance.
I'm sure they would be happy. Just by saying "long distance" now.
It was as if he was saying "long distance" to me.
That's the way of thinking.
There's something interesting.
Yuna's home screen, including her lock screen, is always Nao.
Is that right?
It's always been Nao.
I didn't know that.
I took this picture by surprise.
Ah! I remember now!
I sent it.
I remember now!
It's really something.
It was a sneak peek, right?
It's a spy shot, right?
It's not a picture of me smiling a lot or anything.
It's a picture that's already been taken.
I don't like it! I don't like that picture.
I said something like, "Make sure it's in writing! I said something like, "You know, Nao, you're not the kind of person who smiles like that.
But Nao, you have this kind of smile...
She only shows this kind of smile to me.Only I could see it.
He came to me with a theatrical look on his face, like he was out of it for a moment, and I said
I told him I liked that look.
So that's the one.
He made it his home screen.
That's strange.
So, that's interesting, too.
At the festival the other summer.
I happened to meet you at a festival this summer.
I happened to see you at a festival this summer.
I kept shouting "Nao, Nao, Nao!
In Yamanashi?
It was terrible, wasn't it?
Was it our turn?
Yes, we were.
Just now? We were done at 2:00 p.m.
We had to leave?
We were getting ready.
But I saw you through the window of my dressing room.
Mr. Segi! I was like, "Oh my God, Mr. Segi!
And from the second floor.
This is how it looked from the second floor.
When I took the picture.
It's like a school building.
They were yelling "Nao, Nao!
I thought it was an interesting relationship.
I'm grateful for that.
I have the image of you two being the closest.
With Yuna.
I have the image that everyone is close.
Especially.
Even if we don't say so.
I think we're all thinking the same thing.
Isn't that amazing?
I was surprised the other day.
I bought another pair of sneakers.
We just happened to buy the same pair of sneakers.
You didn't tell him anything?
We didn't talk about it.
I posted the story.
I posted it on my story, and I got a DM.
What? Like, "What?
Wait, we bought one yesterday too.
I bought one yesterday, too.
And then they said...
By accident. Because we bought the same pair of sneakers
I bought the same ones.
And the color?
The color is exactly the same.
And Yuna bought them in Tokyo.
But I bought them in Sendai.
I bought it in Sendai.
What? I was like, "What?
We had the same timing.
We bought the exact same thing.
And we often run into each other.
You mean you run into each other?
We run into each other a lot.
Aren't you afraid?
With someone? Really?
Yes, I am.
It's amazing.
It's strange, isn't it?
It was like that right after you met?
Was it a gradual resemblance?
Or was it from the very beginning?
I think so.
Like what he likes, what he thinks?
Thoughts?
Like, "This is where we are right now.
It fits.
Oh, I see.
That's interesting.
Because, Yuna.
Because?
She'll love it.
Really? I'm glad.
Where do you want to go out alone? What do you like to do?
What do you usually do when you're off the clock?
When I have time.
I have two choices: go out or sleep.
Or sleep at home.
Maybe we're the same.
I either sleep or go out.
I don't really do anything at home.
Home is like a place to sleep.
I understand.
That's right. A place to bathe and sleep.
I might make plans.
Are you an outdoorsman?
I am an outdoorsman.
You do a lot of driving, don't you?
I like it, but I'm a paperboy.
Can you do it?
I don't have one yet.
Yuna said she'd take me.
So let's go with the three of us.
Yuna, did you take pictures? Yes, I did.
Yes, she took me for a ride once.
I've taken her for a ride once. - Really? How was it?Really? How was it?
I mean, even then you said you hadn't driven in a while, so...
I think I can go pretty well.
Let me give you a ride.
I'll be your driver.
So you're an outdoorsman?
But lately I've been getting into it.
Why?
I don't know why.
I'm finding that I'm more comfortable at home.
It's not good.
What are you doing at home?
What do you mean by comfortable?
Sleeping is good.
And watching cartoons.
That's it?
But I don't want to.
I want to be outdoors.
I had Corona, too, so I couldn't get out of the house.
I couldn't get out.
I was watching it then, but...
You have to watch movies and cartoons and stuff.
Yeah, but...
But if you're the type of person who goes out, it might be a good fit for you.
But playing in Sendai is limited.
I don't have a driver's license.
I don't even have a driver's license.
If I had a driver's license, I would like to go anywhere.
But I don't have much time off in Tokyo.
I see.
What do you do? Is it a schedule all the time?
I'm on a schedule.
He's going home after.
He said he feels sorry for her.
She's not here?
Seriously?
The other day, when I was off duty in Tokyo for the first time in a while.
I went out to dinner with him every time.
Don't you have any free time?
No, I don't.
You finish in the evening and can go out for dinner at night?
We would go out with the members and go home.
And then we would go home.
You guys are good friends.
We are always together. Even when we go to Tokyo.
Do you often hang out privately?
With the members.
I think so.
That's right.
We also meet locally for local companies.
At first, we arranged the time of Shinkansen.
But now everyone is scattered.
I don't know when they are coming back.
I don't know when they're coming back. I'm surprised.
But it's so close.
After work.
I'd see him when I go out to eat after work.
And you might run into him at the restaurant.
I see.
But I get that a lot. Are you guys too close?
That's amazing.
Really?
Really.
I can't imagine them in private, so I'm surprised.
Don't you ever get bored?
You don't get bored?
Whenever something interesting happens...
I share it with him.
Of course I don't know.
I don't know if there's something there.
But really...
Open.
You guys are amazing.
You can't all go together, can you?
All of us? But they just go with the flow.
They're just going with the flow.
All of us? How many people are there?
Nine.
Like the one in Tokyo.
You have to make a reservation to get in, don't you?
They want to be together.
That's right.
If there's going to be five of us, let's all go together.
Like a student group? Yes, it is.
We had a tour this year, and there is a lot of free time in a tour.
Sightseeing time. We were nine at that time. The whole time.
That's amazing. You guys are so close.
I wanted to include Yuzuki in the group. Yuzuki said he had lived his life in a group.
But when he joined the group, the other members all loved the solo code so much.
I was confused. For a few years.
He had been struggling with it for several years.
And recently, as an adult, I started to realize that it might be good to be alone, and I got used to it, but
Maybe Yuzuki is better suited for Touhoku-san.
Maybe I like Yuzuki.
Is this a gyaru mindset?
Gyaru tend to cluster together, don't they?
Yes, they do. Yes, they do.Yes, they do. They flock together.
There are quite a lot of gals from the Tohoku region.
Maybe that's why.
It's not because of the way they look, but because of their mindset.
So they are Gyaru in mind.
Maybe that's why.
It's like a group of ghosts.
I think it'll definitely be fun.
Donkey, it's that way. Definitely.
Donkey, donkey, donkey.
It's that way. Absolutely.
I'm sure it's fun.
So that's how it is. It's totally different. Localism.
It seems like the first half is about this much.
It seems there is a first half and then a second half.
So for now, that's it for the first part, the first half, the first half.
Sakura Oto of Team Statch.
I was Waka Yasumori from Inari Tohoku.
Bye bye.